(Sheldon:)-It appears to be a Lord of the Rings ring.
LEONARD: Oh.
(Raj:)It's even got the Elvish engraving on it.
(Sheldon:)It's not Elvish.
(Sheldon:)It's the language of Mordor
written in Elvish script.
"One ring to rule them all."
"One ring to find them."
"One ring to bring them all."
"And in the darkness, bind them."
(Raj:)Holy crap, are we nerdy.
(Howard:)So I was doing some checking
on the ring....
(Raj:)Hold on. Sheldon,
is there ketchup on that table?
(Sheldon:)Yes, there is. Oh, here's a fun fact.
(Sheldon:)Ketchup started out as a general term
for sauce...
...typically made of mushrooms
or fish brine with herbs and spices.
(Sheldon:)Some popular early main ingredients
included blueberry, anchovy...
(Sheldon:)...oyster, kidney bean and grape.
(Raj:)No, that's okay, I'll get it.
(Howard:)Listen, I was looking at the ring
and it seemed a little weird.
(Howard:)No copyright notice on it.